muxy.io 2019-05-26

# Muxy | Home

  1. **Introduction**

Hello again!  By now, you’ve read our [Terms of Service](https://muxy.io/terms/).  If you haven’t, please do so immediately.  Done?  Cool.  Let’s talk about your rights on the Interwebz as they relate to Muxy.

  2. **Definitions**

Throughout this Privacy Policy, we may use certain words or phrases, and it is important that you understand the meaning of them.  We know you’re smart and these words are pretty obvious, but our big fancy city lawyers told us we have to mention them nonetheless.  The list is not all-encompassing and no definition should be considered binding to the point that it renders this Privacy Policy nonsensical:

“Muxy” “ Us” “We” refers to our company, known as “Muxy, Inc”; our Site; our Service; or a combination of all or some of the preceding definitions, depending on the context of the word;

“Service” refers to the services that we provide through our Site, including our alerts, notification, and analytics systems, as well as our Site itself;

“Site” refers to our website,[ http://muxy.io](http://muxy.io/); and our Twitch Extensions;

“User” refers to anyone who uses our Service, including registered users, general visitors to our Site, and anybody who so much thinks of clicking on our Site;

“You” as in, “Hey, you!” refers to you, the person who is governed by this Privacy Policy.

  3. **Information Collected**

Identifying Information

We collect certain personal information from you when you sign up to our Service that can be used to identify you, such as your name, e-mail address, PayPal address (if different from e-mail address), subscriber list, and any other information that we need to collect from you in order to provide our Service or which you provide to us voluntarily (so information you provide under hypnosis doesn’t count).  The information we collect from you, to the extent that it is private, is disclosed only in accordance with our Terms of Service and/or this Privacy Policy.  Since you are not sending us any individual health information, we are not going to make any attempt to comply with the Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act of 1996 (“HIPPA”).

Non-Identifying Information

Whenever you visit our Site, we may collect non-identifying information from you, such as your IP address, referring URL, browser, operating system, cookie information, and Internet Service Provider.  Without a subpoena, voluntary compliance on the part of your Internet Service Provider, additional records from a third party, or a gypsy who’s really good at telling fortunes, this information alone cannot usually be used to identify you.

  4. **Use of Your Information**

We may use your information to:

  * Enhance or improve user experience, our site, or our service.
  * Process transactions.
  * Send e-mails about our site or respond to inquiries.
  * Send e-mails and updates about Muxy, including news and updates about amended legal documents such as this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service.
  * Perform any other function that we believe in good faith is necessary to protect the security or proper functioning of our Site or Service.

  5. **Accessing, Editing, and Removing Your Information**

Users may in some cases be able to review and edit the personal information they have provided to us by logging into your account on the Site and editing their account.  Although most changes may occur immediately, information may still be stored in a web browser’s cache.  We take no responsibility for stored information in your cache, or in other devices that may store information, and disclaim all liability of such.  In addition, we may, from time to time, retain residual information about you in our backup and/or database.  So don’t post anything that would make your mom cry or your boss fire you because even if you delete it, we can’t guarantee some crazy stalker hasn’t already copied it and posted it elsewhere on the Internet.

  6. **Cookies**

We use cookies (you know, those small bits of data sent from a website and stored on a user’s computer) to remember your preferences and to appease Santa Claus along with a glass of milk so he brings us presents in future years.  For these reasons, it is necessary that you enable cookies in your browser, and you hereby acknowledge that we have informed you of our use of cookies and that you consent to our use of cookies in relation to your computer system.

  7. **Third Party Websites**

Muxy may post links to third party websites on its Site.  These third party websites are not screened for privacy or security issues by Muxy because we’d go broke trying to do that, and you release us from any liability for the conduct of these third party websites.

Please be aware that this Privacy Policy, and any other policies in place, in addition to any amendments, does not create rights enforceable by third parties or require disclosure of any personal information relating to members of the Service or Site.  Muxy bears no responsibility for the information collected or used by any advertiser or third party website.  Please review the privacy policy and terms of service for each site you visit through third party links.  Be cautious if a third party site tells you that you’ve won a lottery you don’t remember entering, asks for your financial information, and promises to pay you in rubles.

  8. **Third Party Access to Your Information**

Although you are entering into an Agreement with Muxy to disclose your information to us, we do use third party individuals and organizations to assist us, including contractors, web hosts, and others.

Throughout the course of our provision of our Service to you, we may delegate our authority to collect, access, use, and disseminate your information.  For example, our web host stores the information that you provide us, and we may hire outside contractors to perform maintenance or assist us in securing our website.

It is therefore necessary that you grant the third parties we may use in the course of our business the same rights that you afford us under this Privacy Policy.  For this reason, you hereby agree that for every authorization which you grant to us in this Privacy Policy, you also grant to any third party that we may hire, contract, or otherwise retain the services of for the purpose of operating, maintaining, repairing, or otherwise improving or preserving our website or its underlying files or systems.  You agree not to hold us liable for the actions of any of these third parties, even if we would normally be held vicariously liable for their actions, and that you must take legal action against them directly should they commit any tort or other actionable wrong against you.

Without limiting the generality of the foregoing, you authorize us to collect, share, store, and otherwise use your information.

  9. **Release of Your Information for Legal Purposes**

At times it may become necessary or desirable to Muxy, for legal purposes, to release your information in response to a request from a government agency or a private litigant (known in highly-technical legal language as “the Five-O”).  You agree that we may disclose your information to a third party where we believe, in good faith, that it is desirable to do so for the purposes of a civil action, criminal investigation, or other legal matter.  In the event that we receive a subpoena affecting your privacy, we may elect to notify you to give you an opportunity to file a motion to quash the subpoena, or we may attempt to quash it ourselves, but we are not obligated to do either.  We may also proactively report you, and release your information to, third parties where we believe that it is prudent to do so for legal reasons, such as our belief that you have engaged in fraudulent activities, or necessary to protect legal rights, personal/real property, the personal safety of Muxy, Inc (including our users, employees, and affiliates).  You release us from any damages that may arise from or relate to the release of your information to a request from law enforcement agencies or private litigants.

  10. **Commercial and Non-Commercial Communications**

By providing information to the Site that forms the basis of communications with you, such as contact information, you waive all rights to file complaints concerning unsolicited e-mails from Muxy since, by providing such information, you agree to receive communications from us or anyone else covered under this Privacy Policy.  However, you may unsubscribe from certain communications by notifying Muxy that you no longer wish to receive solicitations or information and we will endeavor to remove you from the database.

  11. **Security Measures**

We take certain measures to enhance the security of our Site and Service, including using SSL certificates, vulnerability scanning, and fiercely loyal pit bulls chained to our server hardware.  However, we make no representations as to the security or privacy of your information.  It is in our interest to keep our Site secure, but we recommend that you use anti-virus software, firewalls, and other precautions to protect yourself from security threats.

  12. **Your California Privacy Rights**

Muxy permits residents of California to use its Service, even though they’re probably all too busy surfing and driving hybrids to know what a computer is.  Therefore, it is the intent of Muxy to comply with the _California Business and Professions Code_ §§ 22575-22579.  If you are a California resident you may request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to any third parties for their direct marketing purposes.  Various provisions throughout this Privacy Policy address requirements of the Californian privacy statutes.  In summary, you must presume that we collect electronic information from all visitors.  You may contact us at team@muxy.io with any questions.

  13. **International Transfer**

Your information may be transferred to—and maintained on—computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction.  If you are located outside of the United States and choose to provide information to us, Muxy transfers Personal Information to the United States via the Internet and/or carrier pigeons, one electron at a time, and processes it there.  Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

  14. **Amendments**

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time.  When we amend this Privacy Policy, we will e-mail you to inform you that there has been an amendment and update this page accordingly.  Your continued use of our Service shall constitute your acceptance of any such amendments.

  15. **Contact Information**

Questions about the Privacy Policy should be messaged to [team@muxy.io](mailto:team@muxy.io).

Last Modified:  May 24, 2017 ****
